<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>autonomous vehicles on Antonino DiMaggio</title><link>https://antoninodimaggio.com/tags/autonomous-vehicles/</link><description>Recent content in autonomous vehicles on Antonino DiMaggio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antoninodimaggio.com/tags/autonomous-vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Northern Canada</title><link>https://antoninodimaggio.com/northern-canada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antoninodimaggio.com/northern-canada/</guid><description>Figure. 1: Source Climate change is warming northern Canada fast. On one hand, a warmer north entails the destruction of inuit traditions, sea level rise, and the disappearance of unique ecosystems. On the other hand, climate change presents a huge economic opportunity for an area that has traditionally lacked both government and private investment. Higher latitudes are warming disproportionately fast compared to the rest of the world; widespread adoption of renewable energy and electric vehicles are not going to stop this.</description></item><item><title>Posts</title><link>https://antoninodimaggio.com/posts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antoninodimaggio.com/posts/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Blatant Statements</title><link>https://antoninodimaggio.com/blatant-statements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antoninodimaggio.com/blatant-statements/</guid><description>People love to argue about statements that are either blatantly true or blatantly false. It seems idotic that people would, for example, argue on Twitter for hours on end over a statement that is completely false. These arguments, however, are not idiotic. They are a result of human nature.
Paul Graham says “The statements that make people mad are the ones they worry might be believed” — this also applies to statements that people worry might not be believed.</description></item><item><title>Integrating Renewables Into The Grid With Machine Learning</title><link>https://antoninodimaggio.com/integrating-renewables-into-the-grid-with-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antoninodimaggio.com/integrating-renewables-into-the-grid-with-machine-learning/</guid><description>Renewables, such as solar (photovoltaics) and wind, have reached economies of scale and, in some cases, are already cheaper than more traditional power plants burning coal and natural gas. To simplify the conversation, I will focus on utility-scale solar without batteries.
Solar has made huge strides over the past decade; with each passing year there are more efficient methods to manufacture and maintain photovoltaic systems. This is all driven by competition.</description></item><item><title>Predict Vehicle Speed Using Dense Optical Flow</title><link>https://antoninodimaggio.com/predict-vehicle-speed-using-dense-optical-flow/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antoninodimaggio.com/predict-vehicle-speed-using-dense-optical-flow/</guid><description>I stumbled across the comma.ai speed challenge so I decided to give it a shot. There are two dashcam videos: one video is used for training (20,400 frames @ 20 FPS) and the other video is used for testing (10,798 frames @ 20 FPS). The training video is accompanied by the ground truth speed at each frame. The objective is to predict the speed of the test video at each frame.</description></item><item><title>Introductions Are In Order</title><link>https://antoninodimaggio.com/introductions-are-in-order/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://antoninodimaggio.com/introductions-are-in-order/</guid><description>I have always liked writing but I have never really found a comfortable place to do it. At university I felt burdened by a laundry list formalities. On social media I feel no sense of permanence or order. A blog generally solves some of these problems. I can write in my own style without penalty and everything is in one organized place.
I plan on writing about machine learning, renewable energy, and everything in between.</description></item></channel></rss>